<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
  xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://hl7.org/fhir ../../input-cache/schemas-r5/fhir-single.xsd">

  <!--<div>
    {% include list-operationdefinitions.xhtml %}
  </div>-->

  <h3>Mobile Patient Identifier Cross-reference Query [ITI-83]</h3>

  <h4>Swiss Operation Definitions</h4>
  <div>
    <ul>
      <li>
        <a href="OperationDefinition-CH.PMIR.html">Find patient matches using IHE-PMIR Profile</a>
        <p>Find patient matches using IHE-PMIR Profile</p>
      </li>
    </ul>
  </div>

  <h4>IHE Operation Definitions</h4>
  <div>
    <ul>
      <li>
        <a href="OperationDefinition-IHE.PIXm.pix.html">Find patient matches using IHE-PIXm Profile</a>
        <p>A Master Patient Index (<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Enterprise_master_patient_index">MPI</a>    ) is a service used to manage patient identification in a context where multiple patient    databases exist. Healthcare applications and middleware use the MPI to match patients    between the databases, and to store new patient details as they are encountered. MPIs    are highly specialized applications, often tailored extensively to the institution's particular    mix of patients. MPIs can also be run on a regional and national basis.   To ask an MPI to match a patient, clients use the &quot;$match&quot; operation, which    accepts a patient resource which may be only partially complete. The data provided is    interpreted as an MPI input and processed by an algorithm of some kind that uses the data    to determine the most appropriate matches in the patient set.  Note that different MPI    matching algorithms have different required inputs. The generic $match operation does    not specify any particular algorithm, nor a minimum set of information that must be provided    when asking for an MPI match operation to be performed, but many implementations will    have a set of minimum information, which may be declared in their definition of the $match    operation by specifying a profile on the resource parameter, indicating which properties    are required in the search.  The patient resource submitted to the operation does not    have to be complete, nor does it need to pass validation (i.e. mandatory fields don't    need to be populated), but it does have to be a valid instance, as it is used as the reference    data to match against.</p>
      </li>
    </ul>
  </div>

</div>